Silvia Zveiter Rocha

Setúbal - Setúbal - Postal Code: 2900-447

🛘 (+55) 22-9-9203-8204 | 🗷 szalbuque@gmail.com | 🖸 szalbuque | 🛅 silvia-zveiter-de-albuquerque-rocha | 🕲 silvia.zveiter.albuquerque.rocha

"I have dedication and responsibility in my work. I move well between business needs and the use of technology. I am motivated by challenges and opportunities for learning and professional growth."

Bio

I have experience administering Windows and Linux servers on premises. Also, I am experienced with technical support to users. I work to improve the knowledge I have with a focus on cloud services administration. My ability to communicate with people from different backgrounds, connecting and empowering them, leads to a pleasant and collaborative work environment. Furthermore, I tend to remain calm in the midst of a crisis, carefully analyzing the problem and possible solutions.

Experience _____

Câmara Municipal de Nova Friburgo/RJ

Rio de Janeiro - Brasil

Mai. 2007 - until now

IT MANAGER

- Configuration and administration of Linux and Windows servers
- Analysis and optimization of administrative process
- Requirement analysis for information systems
- Technical support team leader
- Technologies: Linux and Windows Servers; Active Directory; bash scripts; Hyper-V; PfSense; LibreOffice.

ESPM (Escola Superior de Propaganda e Marketing)

Rio de Janeiro, Brasil

IT MANAGER

Jul. 1999 - Jan. 2006

- · Administration of Windows servers and desktops
- Technical support team leader
- · Analysis and optimization of administrative process
- Support on legacy systems migration
- Technologies: Windows Server; Microsoft Proxy Server; HTML+CSS+Perl; Internet Explorer Admin Kit; Active Directory; Microsoft Office

COMLURB - Companhia de Limpeza Urbana

Rio de Janeiro, Brasil Nov. 1998 - Jun. 1999

SYSTEMS ANALYST

- Analysis and development of operational system
- Technologies: Visual Basic + SQL Server

Education

UFF - Universidade Federal Fluminense

Brasil

MASTER IN PRODUCTION ENGENEERING

2003 - 2004

• Emphasis on information systems

ESPM (Escola Superior de Propaganda e Marketing)

MBA EM MARKETING

• Marketing for business administration

UFF (Universidade Federal Fluminense)

Brasil

BACHELOR IN COMPUTER SCIENCE

1986 - 1990

· Strong scientific and technological background

Technical Skills

Operating systems Ms Windows Server, Linux

Tools and technologies GitHub, Azure, GCP, Docker, Kubernetes

> **Databases** MySQL

Programming languages Javascript, HTML, CSS, Java, Python

Languages Inglês - B1

SILVIA ZVEITER ROCHA MARCH 1, 2023

Courses_____

Dez-2022 Bootcamp Google Cloud DevOps, Digital Innovation One	dio.me
Oct-2022 Oracle One: Software development Front-End Java, Alura Online	alura.com.br
Jun-2022 Agile management: leading change in an agile environment, Alura Online	alura.com.br
Jul-2020 Data Analysis Bootcamp, IGTI	igti.com.br
Jun-2020 Python for data science , Linkedin	linkedin.com
Apr-2020 IT infrastructure and cloud computing, IGTI	igti.com.br
Mai-2019 Advanced Microsoft Excel, ECG/TCE-RJ	RJ - Brasil
Nov-2018 Knowledge management, ECG/TCE-RJ	RJ - Brasil
Jul-2011 Linux Network Server Linux System Admin Linux Essentials, 4Linux	4Linux.com.br
Aug-1999 Official Training Microsoft Windows Server: installation, configuration and administration, Infnet	infnet.com.br

Honors & Awards _____

DOMESTIC

2023 **1st Place**, Digital Innovation One and Banco Carrefour Bootcamp CI/CD Competition

Remote

Additional information _____

Mobility Valid passport; moving to Portugal in March-2023